'''A data file that holds all the questions and answers for the quiz.'''
# question_data = [
#     {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]

# data pulled from website: https://opentdb.com/api_config.php
# Actual data on: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&category=15&difficulty=easy&type=boolean
question_data = [{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Luigi is taller than Mario?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Activision created Battlefield 1.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},
                 {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}
]